■
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
是国安局的鲍勃·科内尔打来的电话
That was bob cornell at nsa.
他们检测到另一个防火墙漏洞
They've detected another firewall breach.
是另一次攻击吗
There's been another attack?
还没确认  但CIP装置已被启用
Not yet, but they believe the cip device is being utilized.
我们必须假定杜巴库在酝酿另一次攻击
We have to assume dubaku is initiating another attack.
-总统阁下  -什么事  蒂姆
- Madam president. - What is it, tim?
我刚接到一个加密电话
I've just been forwarded a scrambled call.
是杜巴库上校打来的
It's from colonel dubaku.
他要和你通话
He's demanding to speak with you.
我给你军队撤离的
The deadline for your forces
最后期限已经过了
To begin their withdrawal has passed.
到窗口去
Go to the window.
看你都做了什么
See what you have done.
要么在一小时内照我说的做
Comply with my demands within the hour,
否则1万多美国人会因此丧命
Or 10,000 more americans will die.
她正上楼
She's on her way up.
事后我给你打电话
I'll call you when it's done.
泰勒先生  你没事吧
Mr. taylor, are you okay?
声音鉴证组分析了录音
Audio forensics cleaned up the recording.
沃克无足轻重
Walker is extraneous.
到这之前杀了她
Kill her before you get here.
拉里  这么做不值得
Larry, I don't think it's worth it.
已没有什么线索了
There's nothing here.
好吧
All right. fine,
去帮詹尼斯和国安局吧
Help janis coordinate with nsa.
她是个优秀的探员
She was a good agent.
她还生死未卜呢
We don't know that she's dead yet!
我把我的一切都贡献给了调查局
I've devoted my life to the bureau
而你却要我相信
And you just expect me to believe
整个政府都腐朽不堪
That the entire government's been corrupted.
也不全是
Not all of them.
在找到主谋前  我们不能相信任何人
But until we find out who, we can't trust anyone.
凭你们四个就能阻止这一切吗
And the four of you really think you can stop this?
我们必须这么做
We have to.
就这么简单
It's as simple as that.
杜巴库想要你们夫妻俩
Dubaku wants you and your wife.
这就是交易条件
That's the deal.
你要冒险把我们
You're asking us to risk our lives
交给杜巴库吗
To be delivered into dubaku's hands.
听他说完  乌勒
Listen to him, ule.
我们怎么能相信这个人
But how can we trust this man?
因为
Because
他没有理由撒谎
He has no reason to lie.
最近怎么样  托尼
How are you doing, tony?
还不错
All right.
爱默生在哪里
Where's emerson?
死了
He's dead.
你还想不想要马托波
You want matobo or not?
你得到了你想要的
You got what you came for.
现在给我滚
Now, get the hell out of here.
一切进展顺利吗
Did everything go smoothly?
马托波夫妇在我们手中  这才是关键
We have the matobos, that's what matters.
我在广播中听到了飞机的事
I heard about the planes on the radio.
白宫方面还没有屈服
The white house still has not complied.
你想怎么做
What do you intend to do?
给他们点颜色看看
Exactly what we promised.
一切就绪  长官
We're ready, sir.
目标定位在哪
Where's the target located?
俄亥俄州的汲沦谷镇
Kidron, ohio.
-人口有多少  -3万人
- Population? - 30,000.
伤亡人数将会很高
Casualties will be high.
开始
Begin.
以下事件发生在下午两点到三点之间
拉里
Larry.
这应该是绑架马托波用的卡车
We think this is the truck the matobos were abducted in.
哪里拍摄的图像
Where was this image taken?
北林机场附近
Near northwoods airfield.
可以追踪到吗
Were you able to track it?
超出这个区域就不行了
Not beyond this sector.
不过他们正沿麦金利大街往东开
But they were heading east on mckinley avenue.
很好  把汽车信息分发给
All right. make sure the vehicle i.d.
所有搜索小组
Is disseminated to all search teams
-和当地特工机构  -遵命  长官
- And local agencies. - Yes, sir.
-拉里  我有线索了  -说吧
- Larry, I think I found something. - Yeah?
我和国安局合作  进行逆向追踪
I've been working nsa, trying to back-trace the cip attack
找到了攻击飞机的
That took down the two planes.
CIP模块的编码碎片
And I found a code fragment
可能是CIP入侵留下的残余信息
Which I think could be residue from the cip intrusion.
我正进行模式匹配
I'm running a pattern match right now.
运气好的话
With any luck at all,
我们或许可以预测到
We may be able to anticipate where in the infrastructure
下一个攻击目标
They're targeting next.
我需要西恩帮忙
And I need sean.
詹尼斯  我不想浪费人手
Janis, I don't want to waste personnel
做徒劳的工作
On some wild-goose chase.
杜巴库威胁要在30分钟内
Dubaku's threatened to kill 10,000 more americans
杀死一万多美国人
In the next 30 minutes.
我明白
I understand that,
要是行不通的话我会立刻放弃
And I will drop it the minute it feels cold.
好吧  我要向白宫作简报  随时向我汇报
All right, I'm going to brief the white house. keep me in the loop.
西恩
Sean.
你觉得他有能力解决这次危机吗
Are you sure he's up to running this operation?
-拉里没问题的  -真的吗
- Larry's fine. - Is he?
是你告诉我他和蕾妮的事
You're the one who told me about him and renee.
这事对他打击很大
This has got to be hitting him pretty hard.
如果我觉得拉里无法胜任工作
If I don't think larry can do his job,
我会告诉你  好吗
I'll let you know, all right?
同时  我要你再打开一个新端口
In the meantime, I need you to open up a fresh socket.
您已接通布莱恩·盖奇探员的电话
You've reached agent brian gedge.
请留言  我会回电
Please leave a message and I'll get back to you.
盖奇探员
Agent gedge,
我在等你回话
I expected to hear from you by now.
我要马上和第一先生谈话
It's urgent that I speak with the first gentleman
情况紧急
As soon as possible.
给我回电  盖奇探员
Call me back, agent gedge.
非常重要
This is extremely important.
请讲
Yes?
联邦调查局的拉里·莫斯找您
Larry moss with the fbi.
什么情况  拉里
Where are we, larry?
我们找到了那辆
We've i.d.'d a vehicle
绑架马托波的货车
That we believe was used in the matobos' abduction.
目前还在追踪中
We're still trying to track it down.
还要多久
And how long is that going to take?
我很想回答您  长官  但我也不知道何时
I wish I could tell you, sir. I don't have a time frame.
这样不行  拉里
That's not good enough, larry.
除非你有所发现  我们才能进攻
Unless you get some results, we're going to get hit again.
找不到杜巴库
A lot of people are going to die
就会死很多人
If you don't find dubaku.
我明白  长官
With all respect, sir,
无需您提醒
I don't need to be told what's at stake.
我们正在全力以赴
We're giving everything we can.
我们中的一个探员已经牺牲了
One of our agents has given her life.
是的  我已经知道了
Yes, I was told about that.
我很遗憾
I'm... I'm sorry.
一有情况就马上通知您
I'll call you the minute we have something.
保持联系
We'll be waiting.
天呐
God....
马托波夫妇被带进一栋建筑
The matobos have been taken into a building.
亚当斯街546号
546 adams.
-好的  把相关资料传给我  -正在传
Okay, pull up the stats on that address. on it.
瑞特大厦  总共4层
It's the ritter building, four stories high.
造了有2年
The building is two years old.
-把安全标准告诉我  -稍等
Give me the security specs. give me a minute.
我们马上就到
We're coming up on it.
我需要你的帮忙
I'm going to need your help.
你找到攻击目标了
I see you've chosen a target.
俄亥俄州的汲沦谷镇旁的博伊德化工厂
The boyd chemical plant near kidron, ohio.
CIP装置已经帮我们
The cip device has enabled us
控制了主储气罐
To take control of the main tank.
我们让主安全阀门失灵
We're about to cause the primary safety valves to fail.
还记得我们上次的会面吗  乌勒
Do you remember the last time we saw each other, ule?
是在你家的晚宴上
It was at a state dinner in your residence.
我们开了瓶好酒
We shared an excellent bottle of wine.
我向你伸出友谊之手
I offered my hand in friendship
你却拒我于千里之外
And you... slapped it away.
你只想让我成为傀儡
You gave me an ultimatum--
为你的军队服务
To be the puppet for your military.
作为一个总理
You could have had a long and prosperous career
你本应该前途无量
As prime minister.
但现在你却将作为叛国贼
But now you're going back to sangala
而返回桑加拉
As a traitor to your people.
我是总理
I am prime minister.
是人民选举出来的
I was elected by the people.
你和朱玛才是叛国贼
It's you and juma who are the traitors.
不
No.
我们给桑加拉带来希望
We brought order to sangala,
但你却要破坏
But you are trying to destroy
我们所做的一切
Everything that we've built.
你将会被带回桑加拉  乌勒
You'll be taken back to sangala, ule,
你要向朱玛将军
And you will give general juma
交代出你的叛国贼同党
The names of all your fellow traitors.
我绝不会那样做
I will never do that.
绝不
Never.
相信我  你会的
Believe me, you will.
带走
Take them.
总统有什么反应吗
Any response from the president?
还没
Not yet.
当她看到有美国人横尸街头时
But once she sees dead americans
她就不会那么顽固了
Lying in the street, she will be less stubborn.
我进去了  杰克  正走向前台
I'm inside, jack, approaching the front desk.
收到
Copy that.
马托波夫妇还在3楼吗
Are the motobos still on the third floor?
是的  杰克
Affirmative, jack.
他们被带走了  我还无法确定他们的去处
They're being moved. I'm just not sure where yet.
收到
Copy that.
下午好
Good afternoon.
我是联邦调查局的沃克探员
I'm agent walker with the fbi.
我没有预约
I don't have an appointment,
我是来见罗恩先生和他的合伙人的
But I'm here to see mr. Roane of roane and associates.
-我会通知他们  -事实上  我不想让他们知道
I'll let them know you're here. actually, I don't want to be announced.
我是来这里谈公事的
I'm here on official business.
好吧
All right.
如果有人问起
So as far as you're concerned,
我从来没来过  明白吗
I was never here, understand?
是的  长官
Yes, ma'am.
过了安检
Past security.
朝电梯走去
Heading toward the elevator.
我们正向维修通道走去
We're on our way to the service entrance.
克罗伊  我到3楼了
Chloe, I'm on the third floor.
左边是律师事务所
Law firm is on your left.
马托波夫妇被关在你右边的
On your right is a suite of offices where matobo's
办公室套间
Being held.
我看到了
I see it.
楼梯在你左边走廊尽头
Stairwell's down the hallway to your left.
沃克探员  我们在门口
Agent walker, we're at the door.
门口有一个守卫  可能有武器
There's one guard outside the suite, probably armed.
比尔  看住3楼
Bill, take the third floor.
等我信号
Wait for my signal.
我们走
Go on.
克罗伊  我们到4楼了
Chloe, we're on the fourth floor
在机房里
In what used to be the computer room.
-现在怎么做  -在房屋中央
What now? in the center of the room
有2块可移动的面板
There are two removable panels.
可以进入夹层
This should give you access to the crawlspace.
收到
Copy that.
好的  安全  我们走
Okay, we're clear. let's go.
我们进来了
We're in.
进去
Go ahead
我不该让你来
I should never have allowed you to come with me.
这是个错误
It was a mistake.
这不是你的决定  乌勒
It was not your decision, ule.
我们会没事的
We will be all right.
杰克·鲍尔马上就会到了
Jack bauer will be here soon.
好了
Okay.
我们到供暖系统这了
We're at the heating unit.
好的  杰克  那个系统开始的地方
Okay, jack, there's an airduct
有个通风管道  你看见了么
Leading off that unit; do you see it?
看到了
Yeah.
沿着它找30码远
Follow that for about 30 yards
你会看到一个接线处
Until you see an electrical junction.
左转  再走20码
Make a left, then another 20 yards
在那你能找到通风口
You'll come to the vent.
在那能看到整个屋里的情况
This will give you a view of the entire floor.
马托波夫妇情况如何
And the matobos?
他们被押送到了临近的屋里
They've been moved into a adjacent room
刚刚离开了主要区域
Just off the main area.
好的  收到
Okay, copy that.
行动
Come on.
整个国安局都在检查防火墙
The entire nsa has been combing the firewall
以查找CIP装置造成的下一个漏洞
Searching for the next cip device breach.
如果真有漏洞的话  你不觉得
If this were something, don't you think
他们应该已经找到了么
They'd already know about it?
不帮忙  就别烦我  西恩
I can live without your negativity today, sean.
又出现了  同样的编码碎片
There it is again, that same code fragment.
在俄亥俄州的汲沦谷  那有什么
"kidron, ohio." what's in kidron, ohio?
有什么敏感设施在那么
Any sensitive installations?
杜巴库可能会袭击的
Something dubaku might want to hit?
我也不清楚
I don't know.
国土安全局有个高价值目标数据库
Homeland has a high-value
我正反复核对呢
Target database; I'm cross-checking it now.
好吧  汲沦谷那没什么
Okay. okay, nothing in kidron itself,
但是在邻县
But in the neighboring county there's...
-博伊德化工  -博伊德化工  他们生产什么的
Boyd chemical. boyd chemical. what do they make?
杀虫剂  给我他们的电话
Insecticide. please get me that number.
喂
Hello?
我是联调局的詹尼斯·古德
This is janis gold at fbi. I need to speak
让你们的工厂经理接电话  马上
To your plant manager immediately, please.
女士  我说过了  我是联调局的
Ma'am, as I just stated I'm with the fbi.
这听起来不重要么
Does that sound vaguely important to you?
现在就给我接约翰·布拉诺
Now, connect me to john brunner.
联调局的  好吧  接过来
Fbi? uh, yeah, put her on.
我是约翰·布拉诺
This is john brunner.
喂
Hello.
布拉诺先生  这里是联调局华盛顿总部
Mr. brunner, this is janis gold, fbi,
我是詹尼斯·古德
D.c. bureau.
有什么能为你效劳的
What can I do for you?
我们在查找一些可能的
We've been tracking some possible
防火墙漏洞
Breaches in the government firewall.
防火墙是用来保护装置的
The firewall's designed to protect installations
-就像你的...  -我知道防火墙是什么  宝贝
- Like yours... - I know what it does, honey.
呃  我们追踪到
Um, we have tracked
在汲沦谷地区出现的
And isolated one of these breaches
一个漏洞
In the kidron area.
我想知道  你们现在
I need to know are you experiencing
有什么麻烦吗
Any problems right now?
事实上  我们正在处理一个
As a matter of fact, we're dealing with one right now.
-怎么了  -我们的三个安全阀刚失效了
- What is it? - three of our safety valves just failed
在主储气罐上
On the primary storage tank.
也无法重启了
We're having trouble resetting them.
-罐里装的什么  -甲基异氰酸脂
What's in that tank? methyl isocyanate.
浓缩杀虫剂  剧毒的
It's concentrated insecticide, highly toxic.
能告诉我  到底出什么事了
Can you-- what the hell is this all about?
布拉诺先生  我们有理由相信
Mr. brunner, I have reason
这是一次针对你工厂的
To believe that this is a terrorist attack
恐怖袭击
On your facility.
Terrorist attack?
是的  先生  我要你启动
Yes, sir, I need you to initiate
现场紧急应急程序
On-site emergency procedures
并保持通话
And stay on this line.
关闭那个储气罐
Shut down the tank.
-出什么事了  -快点  快点
What's going on? do it! do it!
我命令你
My authority.
-该死  -怎么了
- Damn. - what is it?
-没反应  -什么意思  再试试
- It's not responding. - what do you mean? try it again.
还是没有
Nothing.
主储气罐的压力正在升高
Pressure in the primary tank is rising.
-该死的  -布拉诺先生
- Son of a bitch. - mr. brunner?
我们无法关闭主储气罐
We cannot shut down the primary tank
它的压力在升高
And the pressure is building.
如果阻止不了的话
If we cannot stop this, we are looking
毒气就会释放到大气中
At atmospheric release.
好的
Okay.
去叫拉里
Get larry.
杜巴库已经袭击了那个工厂
Dubaku has targeted that facility.
我们得通知总统
We need to alert the president.
布拉诺先生
Mr. brunner,
你现在必须开始疏散人群了
you need to begin evacuating people right now
好的  莫斯探员  有事马上通知我
All right, agent moss, keep me apprised.
我马上向总统汇报
I'll speak to the president.
我刚收到一个内部警报
I just received an inter agency alert.
联调局刚发现了杜巴库的下一个目标
The fbi just discovered dubaku's next target.
一个化工厂  是的
A chemical plant, yeah.
我刚跟拉里·莫斯通过电话
I just got off the phone with larry moss.
我得向总统做简报
I need to brief the president.
第一先生跟总统谈过了么
Has the first gentleman spoken with the president?
还没
Not yet.
四十分钟前  我跟盖奇特工说过了
I talked to agent gedge 40 minutes ago.
泰勒先生是唯一能劝说总统
Mr. taylor is the only person who can talk the president
从桑加拉撤兵的人
Into withdrawing our troops in sangala.
这也是阻止袭击的最佳方案
And that is our best way to prevent this attack.
我知道我们需要他
I know we need him.
我等他给我回电话呢
I'm waiting for a call back.
我还是不满意中间的部分  再念一遍
The middle section's still bothering me; read it again.
杜巴库上校和朱玛集团
"colonel dubaku and the juma regime have killed
已经杀害了无数同胞
"countless thousands of their own people,
和数以百计的美国人民
"and now hundreds of our fellow citizens.
让亡者安息  让刽子手接受愤怒的惩罚
They deserve your prayers and your outrage."
我觉得"愤怒"用得有点过了
I think the word "outrage" might be too strong
如果您想让民众
If you're trying to convey
平静下来的话
Calm authority.
愤怒  是唯一一个能表达
"outrage" is the only word
我现在感情的词  它也能代表
To describe how I'm feeling, and how every person
每个美国民众的心情
In this country will be feeling.
美国的人民应该知道真相
The american people deserve the truth.
杜巴库已经杀死了三百个美国人
Dubaku's already killed 300 americans.
天知道他在策划着什么阴谋
God knows what else he has planned.
进来
Come in.
给我们点时间  安吉拉
Could you excuse us, angela?
什么事
What is it?
联邦调查局发现了
The fbi believes they've detected
下一个袭击目标
Where the next attack will take place.
杜巴库想要使俄亥俄州汲沦谷
Dubaku's infiltrated a chemical plant
一家化工厂发生泄露
Just outside of kidron, ohio.
他已经使工厂里的主储气罐的
He's causing the pressure on the facility's
压力达到了临界值
Primary tank to go critical.
如果储气罐破裂  三千多加仑甲基异氰酸脂
If the tank erupts, over 3,000 gallons
就会被释放到空气中
Of methyl isocyanate will be released into the atmosphere.
在风的作用下
Given the prevailing winds,
一片大面积的毒云
A very large, very toxic cloud
将横扫城镇
Will sweep into town.
甲基异氰酸脂
Methyl isocyanate
是一种高浓缩杀虫剂
Is a concentrated insecticide.
即使少量接触  也会造成严重的肺损伤
Even brief exposure causes severe lung damage
和对皮肤的化学烧伤
And chemical burns of the skin.
我们还有多少时间
What's our time frame?
十五分钟内  储气罐就可能破裂
The tank could rupture in less than 15 minutes.
他们已经开始疏散了么
They've begun evacuating?
我们已经在汲沦谷当地
We've already contacted emergency responders
派出了紧急事件反应部队
On the ground in kidron.
但是时间不够 把所有人都救出来
It's just not enough time to get everyone out.
汲沦谷的人口超过三万
Kidron's population's just over 30,000.
预计我们将损失
This projection says that
超过五成的人
We could lose over 50%?
天哪
Oh, dear lord...
现在  唯一阻止这事的办法
Right now, our only chance of stopping this
就是找到杜巴库和CIP装置
Is finding dubaku and the cip device.
准备好了么
You ready?
轻轻地
Quietly.
杰克  我刚截听到一个联调局警报
Jack, I just intercepted
他们找到了杜巴库的下一个袭击目标
An fbi alert identifying dubaku's next target.
俄亥俄州汲沦谷的一个化工厂
A chemical plant near kidron, ohio,
还剩12分钟爆炸  那有三万多人呢
12 minutes from going critical. there are 30,000
杰克  我们得抓紧了
People in that town, jack. we have to hurry.
我们会尽快的
We're moving as fast as we can.
把探测器给我从包里拿出来
Give me the scope out of the bag.
调到夜视状态
Turning scope over to night-vision.
我没看到杜巴库
I don't see dubaku.
发现尼科尔斯了
We've got nichols.
和三个带自动武器的人
Three men with automatic weapons.
还有三个在控制站  很可能也有武器
Three more over at the control station, most likely armed.
收到
Copy that.
杜巴库
That's dubaku.
我们发现杜巴库了
We got dubaku.
克洛伊  你能看到么
Chloe, are you seeing this?
是的  控制站看起来像S型自动再调度装置
Yes. the control station looks like an s-dart.
很强的处理器
It's a really powerful processor.
-应该就是它在驱动CIP装置  -收到
- It could be driving the cip device. - copy.
国安局的机密设施小组
Nsa's classified infrastructure team
-正试图修补防火墙漏洞  -有进展么
- Is trying to plug the firewall breach. - any luck so far?
-目前没有  但还在努力  -他们只有
None so far, but they're staying on it. they have less than
-不到十分钟时间了  -是的  长官
Ten minutes left. they're aware of that, sir,
他们已经尽力了
But they're doing what they can.
现在不行
Not now.
工厂情况怎么样
What's going on at the plant?
我在和他们通话
I'm on with them now.
约翰  你有没有
John? did you try
刷新记忆卡片
Flashing the memory cards?
三次了  宝贝
Three times, honey.
电脑系统已经失控了
We're not in control of the computer system.
我已经叫我的人撤离了
I've already told my people to get the hell out of here.
通常我不允许别人叫我宝贝
Normally, I don't allow people
不过这事可以以后再说
To call me "honey," but we can discuss that later.
听起来你需要放松一下
Yeah, well, it sounds like you need to lighten up.
好的
Good, good.
我正去主储罐室
I'm heading to the primary tank room.
我想试着手动
I'm going to try to manually
释放储气罐的压力
Release some of the pressure.
不顶用的
That's not going to stop it.
是不顶用  不过应该能
No, but it might buy us
给大家的撤离创造一些时间
A few more minutes so people can evacuate.
这工厂里有一千多员工呢
I've got a thousand workers at this facility.
我要对他们的 安全负责
And I am responsible For their safety.
听着  别挂电话
Now look, I need you to stay on the phone.
-我需要你的帮助  -没问题
- I'm going to need some help. - absolutely.
需要我做什么
What can I do?
我的权限不够修改控制图
I don't have access to the override schematics.
看你能不能调出
See if you can pull up
一号储气罐的操作程序
The operating procedures for tank one.
好的  我找到了
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got it.
-我找到了  -好的
I got it right here. all right.
现在找到应急阀的
Now look for the emergency valve
释放顺序
Release sequence.
好
Okay.
阀门释放  我找到了
Uh, valve release. I have it right here.
很好
OK good, now
我需要你做的是
well I need you to do is
等下  这样做会
This, wait, this procedure is going
把主储气罐内的气体
To release the chemical right
直接释放到你所在的房间
Into the primary tank room where you are right now.
我知道
I know that.
我戴着防毒面具呢
I have respiratory gear on.
我没事的  告诉我顺序
I'll be okay, just give me the sequence.
但是那东西能保护你多久呢
But how long will that protect you?
这个你就别担心了  宝贝
Don't worry about it, honey.
好吧
Uh, okay.
-你看到路由器控制面板了吗  -看到了
Are you looking at the routing board? I am.
继续
Go ahead.
从右向左
Set the bus switches
设置总线开关的顺序
To this sequence from left to right
-2  -2
Two. two.
-8  -8
Eight. eight.
-7  -7
Seven. seven.
-4  -4
Four. four.
-3  -3
Three. three.
好了
Done.
次级流量开关
The secondary flow valve
应该在你身后的右侧
Should be behind you and to your right.
你要向顺时针方向旋转
I need you to turn that clockwise please.
好了  完成了
All right. all right, I got it.
很好  一个阀门的压力已经下降了
Okay, that's one valve down,
还剩3个
Three more to go.
反应仓内的压力已接近400帕
Pressure inside the tank is approaching 400 psi.
离储气罐爆裂还有多长时间
How long before the tank ruptures?
7分钟
Seven minutes.
我们有麻烦了
We've got a problem.
-怎么了  -警报响了
What is it? an alert.
我们屋顶的监控显示
Our hidden surveillance camera on the roof.
阿尔梅达和鲍尔来了
Almeida and bauer.
什么时候
When was this taken?
20分钟之前
20 minutes ago.
我以为你已经干掉他们了
I thought you killed almeida and bauer?
该死的  你说这个地方是
Damn it! you said this location
-绝对安全的  -没错
Was kept secret from everyone! it was.
那他们怎么会在这出现
Then what are they doing here?!
-我不知道  -他们怎么找到我们的
I don't know. how did they find us?!
我不知道
I don't know!
压力600帕还在上升中
600 psi and rising.
解除CIP模块
Disengage the cip module.
把它卸下来
Begin the offload.
你在干什么  我们就快成功了
What are you doing? we're almost there.
我们要换个地方继续进攻
We will continue this attack from another location.
让我们完成这次攻击
Let's finish this.
我们能对付他们
We can handle them.
我们必须马上离开这
We need to get out of here now.
CIP模块已经解除  开始卸载
The cip module's disengaged, starting off load.
这到底是怎么回事
Hey, what the hell is that?
到底是怎么了
What the hell is that?!
什么事
What's the matter?
防火墙的漏洞刚刚关闭了
The firewall breach just closed.
什么
What?!
什么意思
What are you talking about?
CIP模块的入侵停止了  防火墙安全了
No cip intrusion, the firewall is secure.
谁干的  国安局吗
How? nsa?
我不知道
I don't know.
拿上CIP模块
Bring the cip module.
带上马托波和他老婆
Get Motobo and his wife!
比尔  我们给他们
Bill, we should go
来个两面夹击
With the second option on the assault.
你和托尼直接从正门进攻
Two-prong attack. you and tony come through the main entrance.
-我们从这进入  -收到
We'll go in from here. copy.
把我背包里的C4炸药拿出来
Give me the c4 out of the bag.
上
Go!
走
Move.
快走
Move!
去拿CIP装置
Get the cip device!
安全
Clear!
这边也安全了  抓到杜巴库了吗
All clear over here! get dubaku?
没有
Negative!
杰克  我拿到CIP装置了
Jack, I've got the cip device.
已经被破坏了
It's been destroyed.
杰克  我是蕾妮  马托波夫妇已获救
Jack, it's renee. the motobos are safe.
我正带他们上货车
I'm taking them to the van.
收到  你和比尔再
Copy that. I want you
彻底清查一下  看能不能找到杜巴库
And bill to do a sweep. see if you can find dubaku.
我负责南面
I'll cover the south side.
约翰  约翰  你还在吗
John? john, are you still there?
是的
Yeah.
约翰  听我说
John, listen to me.
恐怖分子已经脱离系统了
The terrorists are out of the system.
请告诉我目前的情况
Please tell me what is happening right now.
自动关闭模式已经启动
Automatic shutdown mode has kicked in.
压力正在下降
Pressure's dropping.
我想我们没事了
I think we're gonna be all right.
太好了
Okay, that's great.
现在你要马上离开那里
Now you-you gotta get out of there right now.
约翰
John?
我到不了门那了
I can't make the door...
我已经派出营救小组
I'm sending the rescue team.
他们马上就到
A rescue team is on its way.
约翰  坚持住
John, please stay with me.
坚持住
Stay with me.
他们找到杜巴库了吗
Have they found dubaku?
还在搜查
Still searching.
第一支外勤小组5分钟后到  杰克
First responders are five minutes away, jack.
收到
Copy that.
站起来
Get up.
我让你站起来
I said get up!
他们来了
They're coming.
请别逼我这么做了
Please don't make me do this.
我会到你家里  迈克尔
I will go to your home, michael.
我会让你的妻子
I'll make you wife watch
看着我杀死你的女儿
As I kill your daughter,
然后我会杀了她
And then I will kill her.
所以照我说的做
So do as I ask.
才能救你家人
Save your family.
把手举起来
Let me see your hands!
他是拉森
It's latham.
杜巴库在哪
Where's dubaku?!
对不起
I'm sorry.
找掩护
Cover!
托尼  比尔
Tony! bill!
-在  -你没事吧
- Yeah! - you all right?
杰克
Jack?
杰克  收到请回答
Jack, can you hear me?
收到  我们没事
Yeah, yeah, we're okay.
发生什么事了
What happened?
拉森被做成了人体炸弹
Latham was wired with explosives.
我们还是没有找到杜巴库
We still don't have dubaku.
什么
What?
CIP装置已经被破坏了
The cip device has been destroyed.
我要你和马托波夫妇在一起
I want you to stay with the motobos.
保证他们的安全
Make sure they're safe.
杰克  警察马上就到了
Jack the police are almost here.
你要是被抓  整个计划就都泡汤了
If you get arrested, this entire operation goes out the window.
-你必须马上离开那  -收到
You have to get out of there. copy that.
-他跑了  -我们必须回到安全屋
He's gone. we need to get back to the safe house.
我们走
Let's go.
西恩  国家安全局和国土安全局
Sean, this stays both nsa and homeland have no idea
都搞不懂汲沦谷攻击为什么停止了
Why the breach at the kidron plant was stopped.
他们还在查
They're still looking.
我们也在找原因
We're working on it here also.
詹尼斯正在协助数码鉴证组
Janis is coordinating with a digital forensics team
并把工厂的信息发给他们
That she sent over to the plant.
这讲不通啊
This doesn't make any sense.
为什么杜巴库突然停止了这次攻击
Why... why would dubaku suddenly stop an attack
他离成功只差几分钟了
When he was minutes away from causing mass casualties?
或许CIP装置出问题了
Maybe there was a malfunction in the cip device.
不  我不要猜测  我只想知道事实
No, no, I don't want maybes, all right? I want answers.
我们正在全力以赴  先生
We're doing everything we can, sir.
这还不够  不对吗
That's not good enough right now, is it?!
我不知道该说什么了  先生
I don't know what else to tell you, sir.
我知道您对蕾妮的事很不安
I know you're upset about renee,
但是对我发脾气也是无济于事
But getting angry at me is not going to make it go any faster.
如果你认为我是因为沃克探员的事
If you think I'm yelling at you because of my history
而对你大喊大叫  那你就错了
With agent walker, you are mistaken.
成千上万的民众正处于危险之中
There are thousands of lives at stake here.
这才是让我不安的原因
That's what concerns me.
抱歉  先生
Sorry, sir.
我要你和詹尼斯同国安局合作
I want you and janis to work with nsa.
找到CIP装置的具体位置
Find out where that cip device is being used.
只要我们找到装置  就能找到杜巴库
If we find the device, we find dubaku.
谢谢您的来电
I appreciate the call. thanks a lot.
詹尼斯  拉里让你和国安局合作
Janis, larry wants you to interface with nsa.
看能否反追踪到CIP装置的具体位置
See if you can back-trace that cip code fragment to its source.
我试试
I'll try.
你在和谁通话
Who were you talking to?
工厂快速反应小组的负责人
The head of the response team at the plant.
他怎么说
What did he say?
设备已经安全了
Facility's clean.
少量的化学气体发生了泄露
A trace amount of the chemical was released, but not enough
但不足以造成伤害  现场已经被保护起来了
To do any damage, and the site has been secured.
很好
That's good.
那个工厂经理怎么样了
What about the plant manager?
约翰·布拉诺
John brunner.
他没事吧
Is he okay?
不
No.
能帮个忙吗
Will you do me a favor?
说说看
It depends.
我想通知布拉诺先生的家人
I'd like to track down mr. brunner's family.
我是最后一个和他通话的人
I was the last one to speak with him,
我认为应该让他们知道他是多么勇敢
And I feel they should know how brave he was.
我找找看
I'll see what I can find.
谢谢
Thank you.
詹尼斯  在节哀之前
Janis, before you start sending flowers,
你应该先找出CIP装置的具体位置
You need to find out where that cip device was being used.
知道了  我正在找
I know. I'm on it.
清理小组已经到达现场
Cleanup crews are already on site
我们正在进行工厂周围
And we're continuing our evacuation of a one-mile radius
1英里的疏散撤离工作
Around the chemical plant.
伤亡情况呢
Casualties?
实际死亡  只有一人 是工厂的经理
There was, in fact, one casualty, The plant manager.
剩余因化学品烧伤和吸入有毒气体
13 other workers are being treated
而受伤的13名工人已被送去急救
For chemical burns and inhalation of toxic fumes.
再就没有任何针对防火墙的入侵行动吗
And there haven't been any other intrusions in the firewall?
没有了  女士
No, ma'am.
看起来好像危机已经解除了
It appears the crisis has been averted.
除此以外  没人能解释
Except that no one's been able
防火墙为什么又安全了
To explain how the firewall break disengaged.
目前是的
Not yet.
联邦调查局也毫无头绪
The fbi has no idea how it happened... it just happened.
这讲不通
And that's not an explanation.
可能杜巴库正要发布另一个警告
Perhaps dubaku was firing another warning shot.
不可能  杜巴库已经弄下了两架飞机
No, dubaku's already down two planes.
他不会在乎死更多的人
He's not afraid to take more lives.
不管怎么说  我们现在安全了
In any event, we should be grateful.
除非知道真相  否则我是不会
I'm not one to accept good news
接受这样的好消息的
Unless I know where it comes from.
找出真相前  我要维持目前的安全等级
Until we have more answers, I want to maintain alert levels.
什么事
Yes?
总统阁下  史密斯上将在2号线
Madam president, I have admiral Smith on line two.
接进来  谢谢你  蒂姆
Put him through. thank you, tim.
上将
Admiral?
我一直在打盖奇探员的电话  但始终没人接
I've been trying to reach agent gedge, and he hasn't picked up.
是的  我确定号码没错
Yes, I'm sure I have the right number.
一小时前我刚跟他通过话
I just spoke to him over an hour ago.
他说他在萨曼莎·罗斯的公寓外面
He said he was outside samantha roth's apartment
在等第一先生
Waiting for the first gentleman.
找到他
Just find him.
我不管你派谁去
I don't care who you have to pull off shift.
还是联系不上盖奇
Still can't reach gedge.
特勤处也找不到他
The secret service doesn't know where he is either.
我需要告诉总统
I need to tell the president.
或许你得等等
Maybe you should hold off.
目前的危机又升级了
The domestic threat's been lifted for now
她正和史密斯上将通话
And she's on the phone with admiral smith.
我不能批准空中打击
I can't authorize the air strikes
除非我们出兵计划已经妥当
Until our post-invasion plans are in place.
在找到可行性方案之前
Finding a politically viable replacement, until that happens,
我要求军队全面戒备
You need to keep your forces at full readiness.
参谋长们已经等得不耐烦了
The joint chiefs are getting impatient.
总统阁下  我们需要谈谈您的丈夫
Madam president, we need to talk about your husband.
对于令郎的死
His theory about your son's death,
他还是难以释怀
He hasn't let it go.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
他去质询罗杰的女友
He's been harassing roger's girlfriend,
认为她参与了罗杰的谋杀
Accusing her of complicity in the death of roger.
亨利和我跟着联调局
Henry and I went over it
一次又一次地调查
Again and again with the fbi,
后来他向我发誓 他不会再纠结于此了
And he swore to me He was past all that.
他找到了一个迎合他的
Well, he's found a private investigator who's feeding
谋杀理论的私人侦探
His conspiracy theory;
他在被人利用
Taking advantage of him.
请让亨利来听电话
Please get henry on the phone.
恐怕不行
I'm afraid I can't do that.
我联系不上他
Henry's unreachable.
什么意思
I don't understand.
盖奇探员的电话无人接听
Agent gedge hasn't been answering his phone.
我应该早点告诉你的
I probably should have told you before.
你是说我丈夫失踪了吗
You're telling me my husband's gone missing?
特勤组已经发出通告
Secret service has put out an apb.
他们正在去罗斯小姐的家中
They're going to ms. roth's apartment.
无论发生了什么  我都会很快查清
Whatever's going on, I will find out soon enough.
这是代号 查理-0-查理的优先命令
This is a priority order code charlie zero charlie.
需要立即找到盖奇探员
We need an immediate 20 on agent gedge.
所有外勤探员立即出发
All available field agents proceed
至威尔金森路404号 代号 查理-0-查理
404 wilkinson drive. Code charlie zero charlie.
你正在犯错误
You're making a mistake.
好好想想
Think about it.
闭嘴
Shut up!
你没杀过人
You haven't killed anybody yet.
你没必要这么做
You don't need to do this.
盖奇陷害我的计划已经失败了
Gedge's plan to frame me is already blown.
如果你杀了我
If you kill me,
他们就会查出来这是谋杀
They'll know it was murder,
并会由此找到你
And they'll trace it back to you.
说
Go ahead.
盖奇探员去哪了  我联系不到他
Where's agent gedge? I can't reach him.
盖奇死了
Gedge is dead.
出什么事了
What happened?
本应按计划进行
Everything was going according to plan...
但还是了问题
But something went wrong.
泰勒杀了盖奇  我不知道他怎么做到的
Taylor killed gedge; I don't know how.
泰勒先生现在在哪里
Where's mr. taylor now?
在我旁边
He's right here.
别杀他  把他带到我这
Don't kill him, bring him to me.
明白
Yes, sir.
马托波总理  夫人  请跟我来
Prime minister matobo, ma'am, please come with me.
克罗伊  用卫星查看瑞特大厦
Chloe, pull up the ritter building on a satellite grid.
查看杜巴库离开留下的痕迹
Look for any sign of dubaku leaving the site.
我们必须找到他
We've got to find him.
我需要20分钟来设置卫星
It's going to take me 20 minutes to task the satellite.
那就别浪费口舌
Then don't waste time talking about it.
调出卫星和交通摄像头
Pull up satellite and traffic cams,
监视街角和汽车站
Street corners and metro stations.
先干什么
What's the priority?
我一次只能做一件事情
I can only do one thing at a time.
-卫星  -好吧
- Satellite!  - fine.
比尔  我们必须重新考虑一下
Bill, we need to rethink this.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你原计划监控一次卧底行动
You were set up to surveil an undercover operation.
现在卧底身份暴露了
Your cover's been blown.
警察还在找我们
The police are after us.
我们无法在百万人口的城市找一个人
We are not equipped to look for one man in a city of millions.
我们需要其它的资源
We need additional resources.
你有何建议
What are you suggesting?
是时候和外面部门联系了
It's time to contact outside agencies.
-政府吗  -是的
- The government?  - yes.
我记得你说过政府是不可信的
I thought you said the government couldn't be trusted.
现在  我们别无选择
Right now, we don't have a choice.
我们不能相信它
It can't be trusted.
我们不能信任任何人
We can't trust anybody,
这就是为什么我们独自行动
That's why we're working on the outside.
泰勒总统可以被信任
President taylor can be trusted.
我并不怀疑这点  总理
I'm not questioning that, prime minister.
而是她身边的人无法被信任
It's the people around her who can't be trusted.
布坎南先生  杰克是对的  我们需要帮助
Mr. buchanan, jack's right. we need help.
这太危险了
It's too dangerous.
我们可以限制消息的去向
We can limit the flow of information.
总理可以帮我们
Prime minister matobo can get us past
直接向总统解释清楚
Explain to her why and what we're doing.
我觉得杰克是对的
I think jack's right.
我们在那栋楼里留下了太多的痕迹
We left a lot of clues in that building.
我们不能在冒险
We're vulnerable; we can't do this
单干下去了
On our own anymore.
难道我要和你们继续躲下去
Am I supposed to remain in hiding with you,
装成我和我夫人被绑架
Pretend that my wife and i
或被杀了吗
Are still being held hostage or dead?
我必须返回白宫
I need to return to the white house
帮助总统挽救我的国家
And help the president save what's left of my country.
让我的丈夫去吧
Let my husband do this.
让他给泰勒总统打电话
Let him call president taylor.
她会听他的
She will listen to him.
比尔  要想找到杜巴库  让他打电话
Bill, you want to find dubaku, make the call.
好吧
All right.
给我接白宫
Get me the white house.
博伊德化工厂的代表们
Representatives from boyd chemical
向当地政府部门保证
Have assured local authorities
当前危机已经过去了
That the immediate crisis has passed.
但这仍无法缓解汲沦谷镇
However, this has done little to calm the nerves
民众的紧张情绪
Of the citizens of kidron, ohio,
他们中的许多人跑到附近的社区避难
Many of whom have taken shelter in neighboring communities.
我们再次确认只有一人
Again, we have confirmed one fatality
在工厂内死亡
Inside the plant itself.
其它13名博伊德的员工正在当地的
13 others, all boyd employees,
医疗中心接受救治
Are being treated at local medical centers...
-总统阁下  -请讲
- Madam president. - Yes?
马托波总理希望和您通话
I have prime minister matobo calling for you.
马托波
Matobo?!
是的  阁下
Yes, ma'am.
你能追踪电话吗
You're tracing it?
我们试了  总统阁下  但它是保密线路
We tried, madame president, but it's a secure line.
接进来
Put him through.
总理
Prime minister?
是我  总统阁下
Yes, madame president.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
感谢上帝  我和我夫人都好
Thank god my wife and I are both fine.
我们被救了
We were rescued.
被谁
By whom?
你在哪里
Where are you?
一个安全的地方
In a safe place.
总统阁下  请您听我讲
Madame president, you need to listen to me.
救我的人拿到了CIP装置
The people who rescued us, they have acquired the cip device.
它已经被摧毁了
It has been destroyed,
贵国当前的危机已经过去了
And your country is no longer under immediate threat.
他们是谁  告诉我这到底怎么回事
Who are these people, and tell me how this happened.
我会当面向您禀告的
I will tell you everything in person,
但是  必须是私下里
But, uh, this must happen privately.
我必须只和您一人谈
I must speak to you alone.
为什么不能有其他人
Why alone?
他们会带我过去  总统阁下
They will bring me to you, madame president.
我们会在10分钟内到达
We will arrive in ten minutes.
恭候大驾
I'll be waiting for you.
他们试图追踪电话  但没成功
They tried to trace the call, but the line held.
伊桑  马上来见我
Ethan, I need to see you right now.
怎么了  总统阁下
Yes, madame president?
我刚和马托波总理通了电话
I just spoke to prime minister matobo.
什么
What?!
他很安全
He's safe.
怎么回事  发生什么事了
How? what happened?
等他到的时候会告诉我们
He'll let us know when he gets here.
他在路上  他希望私下见面
He's on his way now. he wants a private meeting.
把他从南门带进来
Bring him in through the south entrance,
别走漏了消息
And keep this to as few people as possible.
好的
All right.
杰克  我给你制定了一条到白宫的路线
Jack, I've mapped a route for you to the white house.
大部分是小巷
It's mostly side streets,
但还是有一些交通摄像头
But there will be fewer traffic cams.
好的  发到我手机上
Okay, good. send it to my phone.
准备好了  我们走吧
We're ready. let's go.
我们把车开到楼前
As soon as we set the vehicle in front of the building,
沃克探员就带马托波先生上车
Agent walker will move mr. matobo.
杰克  杰克
Jack... jack!
怎么了
What?
我哪都不去
I'm not going.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
如果政府发现了托尼
If the government gets their hands on tony,
他们会逮捕他
They'll arrest him.
我告诉过你
I already told you--
和比尔合作前我干了不少坏事
I did some pretty bad things before I teamed up with bill.
托尼  相信我
Tony, take it from me...
你必须面对这个结果
You need to deal with the consequences.
你也要相信我  我会的
And believe me, I will.
但不是现在  等抓到杜巴库后
But not yet. not till we get dubaku.
我有条线索
I'm working on a lead.
我找到了爱默生手下的一个小子
I've got a guy on emerson's crew
他或许能提供一些线索
Who might have some intel we can use.
让他继续查吧  杰克
Let him do this, jack.
我们能有今天多亏了他
He's the reason we got this far.
好吧
Fine.
但你得保证这事一结束
But you give me your word as soon as this as over,
你就去自首
You turn yourself in.
我们会支持你的
We'll stand behind you.
好的  我保证
All right, you have my word.
祝你好运  多加小心
Good luck. be careful.
我在上班的路上
I was on my way to work, so I thought
就顺便来看下你
I'd stop in and see you.
我早些时候试图打你手机
I tried calling you earlier.
对不起  今天比较忙
I'm sorry; I've been busy.
你还好吧  你看上去很累
Are you all right? you look exhausted.
今天事多了点
It's just been a long day.
好吧  我还是想你来吃晚餐
Well, I hope you're still coming over for dinner.
我会做烤宽面条
I'm making lasagna.
我姐姐也保证不会再给你脸色看
And my sister promises not to give you any more dirty looks.
你不会忘了吧
You haven't forgotten, have you?
没  没
No. no.
我现在有点事要处理
It's just that I've got some business to attend to.
塞缪尔  你工作太辛苦了
Samuel, you work too much.
每次你来吃晚饭
Every time you come into the dinner,
你总是在接电话
You're always on the phone.
我不得不这么做  玛丽亚
I have to, maria,
只有这样  有一天我才能把你
So that, one day, I can finally take you away
从你工作的鬼地方解救出来
From that awful place that you work in.
我们就是在那鬼地方相识的
Well, we met in that awful place.
你别忘了哦
Don't forget that.
-待会见  -好的
- I'll see you later.  - okay.
讲
Go ahead.
你抓住泰勒了吗
Have you got mr. taylor?
是的  我三分钟后到
Yes. I'm about three minutes away.
我楼的对面有家韩国杂货店
There's a korean grocer opposite my building.
我的一个手下会在那后面见你
One of my men will meet you out back.
把泰勒带进去
Bring taylor inside.
你准备怎么对付他
What are you gonna do to him?
你只管确保自己不被跟踪就行了
Just make sure you weren't followed.